[{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664507710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":47968,"timeElapsed":130950},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664513368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5654,"timeElapsed":136608},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664517405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4032,"timeElapsed":140645},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664531449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":14039,"timeElapsed":154689},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664553885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":22432,"timeElapsed":177125},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664563958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":10068,"timeElapsed":187198},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664570496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6534,"timeElapsed":193736},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664579099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8596,"timeElapsed":202339},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664590335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":11230,"timeElapsed":213575},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664604379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":11927,"timeElapsed":227619},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664608477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4094,"timeElapsed":231716},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664614336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5856,"timeElapsed":237576},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664619723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5383,"timeElapsed":242963},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664629877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10149,"timeElapsed":253116},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664640891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":11009,"timeElapsed":264130},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664645889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4993,"timeElapsed":269128},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664653575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":7680,"timeElapsed":276815},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664664015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":10434,"timeElapsed":287255},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664672820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7095,"timeElapsed":296059},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664676675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3850,"timeElapsed":299915},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664680569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3887,"timeElapsed":303809},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664686904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":6329,"timeElapsed":310144},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664692678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5770,"timeElapsed":315917},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664705060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":12378,"timeElapsed":328300},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664712607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7541,"timeElapsed":335846},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664722760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":10149,"timeElapsed":346000},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664734270,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11505,"timeElapsed":357509},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664742755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":8481,"timeElapsed":365995},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664752358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":7716,"timeElapsed":375598},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664756496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4133,"timeElapsed":379736},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664760432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3929,"timeElapsed":383672},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664770422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":9984,"timeElapsed":393662},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664774473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4043,"timeElapsed":397713},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664781287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6807,"timeElapsed":404527},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664788407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7115,"timeElapsed":411647},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664796771,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8360,"timeElapsed":420011},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664804109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7334,"timeElapsed":427349},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664811923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7809,"timeElapsed":435163},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664820697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":7139,"timeElapsed":443937},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664824139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3438,"timeElapsed":447379},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664828588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4445,"timeElapsed":451828},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664835163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":6568,"timeElapsed":458403},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664839645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4477,"timeElapsed":462885},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664848134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8483,"timeElapsed":471374},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664863295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":15156,"timeElapsed":486535},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664869390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":6089,"timeElapsed":492629},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664876308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":6913,"timeElapsed":499548},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664973429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":94526,"timeElapsed":596669},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664980010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6575,"timeElapsed":603250},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664986311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6295,"timeElapsed":609551},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664993612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7291,"timeElapsed":616852},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664997740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4118,"timeElapsed":620980},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665002646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4900,"timeElapsed":625886},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665011730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9079,"timeElapsed":634970},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665015956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4220,"timeElapsed":639196},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665019892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3931,"timeElapsed":643132},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665045973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":24059,"timeElapsed":669213},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665049444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3468,"timeElapsed":672684},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665054138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4689,"timeElapsed":677377},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665060362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6221,"timeElapsed":683602},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665065202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4835,"timeElapsed":688441},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665076362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":11156,"timeElapsed":699602},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665082842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6475,"timeElapsed":706082},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665086979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":4130,"timeElapsed":710218},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665092722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5739,"timeElapsed":715962},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665103747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":9403,"timeElapsed":726987},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665107383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3632,"timeElapsed":730623},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665110495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3108,"timeElapsed":733735},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665116160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":5660,"timeElapsed":739400},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665119029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2862,"timeElapsed":742268},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665124852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5818,"timeElapsed":748092},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665130626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5768,"timeElapsed":753866},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665135049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4417,"timeElapsed":758289},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665138559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3502,"timeElapsed":761798},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665181424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":41447,"timeElapsed":804664},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665186279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4849,"timeElapsed":809519},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665189665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3382,"timeElapsed":812904},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665195841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6171,"timeElapsed":819081},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665198748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2904,"timeElapsed":821988},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665203936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":5183,"timeElapsed":827176},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665207360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3419,"timeElapsed":830599},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665211665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4301,"timeElapsed":834904},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665216096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4426,"timeElapsed":839336},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665224736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7054,"timeElapsed":847976},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665227685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2944,"timeElapsed":850925},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665231399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3709,"timeElapsed":854639},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665235694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4288,"timeElapsed":858934},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665238973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3273,"timeElapsed":862213},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665242135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3156,"timeElapsed":865375},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665245259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3119,"timeElapsed":868498},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665248040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2777,"timeElapsed":871280},{"subjectID":"y0w1sg96kk","prolificID":"673fd71b6b09975c50e7f38f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216802b6827a5af082a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665251958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3911,"timeElapsed":875198}]